<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gconf>
	<entry name="method" mtime="1284131094" type="schema" stype="pair" owner="liblocation" car_type="string" cdr_type="string">
		<local_schema locale="C" short_desc="A pair of string values that tell the D-Bus service name of the 
        currently active location daemon and the location method used within 
        that daemon">
			<default type="pair">
				<car type="string">
					<stringvalue>com.nokia.Location</stringvalue>
				</car>
				<cdr type="string">
					<stringvalue>las</stringvalue>
				</cdr>
			</default>
			<longdesc>A pair of string values that tell the D-Bus service name of the 
        currently active location daemon and the location method used within 
        that daemon. For BlueTooth devices the location method is the address 
        of the BlueTooth device. For integrated GPS and cellular network –based 
        location the location method is always las. The default value is 
        (com.nokia.Location, las). Examples:
        Integrated GPS and cellular:
        (com.nokia.Location, las)
        BlueTooth GPS:
        (org.freedesktop.Gypsy, 00:0D:B5:34:52:F6)
        </longdesc>
		</local_schema>
	</entry>
	<entry name="disclaimer-accepted" mtime="1284131094" type="schema" stype="bool" owner="liblocation">
		<local_schema locale="C" short_desc="A boolean value that tells whether the user has accepted 
        the location disclaimer or not">
			<default type="bool" value="false"/>
			<longdesc>A boolean value that tells whether the user has accepted 
        the location disclaimer or not. The default value is false, i.e., 
        the user has not accepted the disclaimer. Until the user accepts 
        the disclaimer the device shows the disclaimer dialog whenever 
        an application tries to get location data through the location-*.h API. 
        When set to true, the device doesn’t show the dialog any more.
        </longdesc>
		</local_schema>
	</entry>
	<entry name="network-disabled" mtime="1284131094" type="schema" stype="bool" owner="liblocation">
		<local_schema locale="C" short_desc="A boolean value that tells whether the network-based methods 
        are is disabled or enabled">
			<default type="bool" value="false"/>
			<longdesc>A boolean value that tells whether the network-based methods 
        are is disabled or enabled. The default value is false, i.e., 
        network-based methods are enabled. This setting enables both AGPS 
        and cellular network –based positioning. If the value of both 
        gps_disabled and network_disabled are set to true, the 
        location-control.h API method location_gpsd_control_start causes 
        the enable dialog to be shown. If the user decides to enable network 
        in the dialog, network_disabled is set to false and the system 
        behaves accordingly.
        </longdesc>
		</local_schema>
	</entry>
	<entry name="gps-disabled" mtime="1284131094" type="schema" stype="bool" owner="liblocation">
		<local_schema locale="C" short_desc="A boolean value that tells whether the gps receiver is disabled 
         or enabled">
			<default type="bool" value="false"/>
			<longdesc>A boolean value that tells whether the gps receiver is disabled 
         or enabled. The default value is false, i.e., the gps receiver is 
         enabled. If the value of both gps_disabled and network_disabled are 
         set to true, the location-control.h API method 
         location_gpsd_control_start causes the enable dialog to be shown. 
         If the user decides to enable GPS in the dialog, gps_disabled is 
         set to false and the system behaves accordingly.
         </longdesc>
		</local_schema>
	</entry>
</gconf>
